{
    "subject": "resource/Romaine_Brooks",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Symbolism_(arts)",
    "human_readable": "Romaine Brooks was associated with Symbolism (arts).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9662250876426697,
            "question": "How is Romaine Brooks connected to Symbolism in the arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.961806058883667,
            "question": "What is Romaine Brooks' association with Symbolism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9345783591270447,
            "question": "What art movement was Romaine Brooks associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765949010848999,
            "question": "In which artistic tradition was Romaine Brooks active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765478730201721,
            "question": "What kind of art was Romaine Brooks involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8417292237281799,
            "question": "To which artistic style did Romaine Brooks belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8326522707939148,
            "question": "What artistic period influenced Romaine Brooks' style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8286782503128052,
            "question": "Which art movement did Romaine Brooks contribute to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7936182022094727,
            "question": "Name the art movement that Romaine Brooks is known for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6585724949836731,
            "question": "Which art movement characterized Romaine Brooks' work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Romaine Brooks was associated with Symbolism (arts).",
            "html": "dbpedia_8319_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the art movement that Romaine Brooks is known for.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8319_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which art movement did Romaine Brooks contribute to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8319_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What artistic period influenced Romaine Brooks' style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8319_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8319_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Romaine Brooks was associated with Symbolism (arts)\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Romaine Brooks' style defies classification, but she has been most frequently linked to the movements of Aestheticism and Symbolism because of her leaning towards the non-narrative and the romantic and lyrical qualities of her portraits. This suggests a connection between Brooks and the art movement Symbolism."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Romaine Brooks has been frequently linked to the movements of Aestheticism and Symbolism due to her leaning towards non-narrative, romantic, and lyrical qualities in her portraits. This supports the triple stating that Romaine Brooks was associated with Symbolism."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}